<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<data>
<home_page>
	<slogan>Unique, best-in-class and intimate corporate finance advisory services to Middle East businesses and corporations</slogan>
</home_page>
<about_us_page>
	<main_text>We think, advise and execute in the best interest of the client as though we were the owners of the business</main_text>
	<bubble>Independent corporate finance advisory firm, founded by a team of highly experienced investment bankers from global, world-class, bulge-bracket firms</bubble>
	<bubble>Unique, best-in-class corporate finance advisory services to family-owned and entrepreneurial businesses and corporations in the Middle East embarking on transformational transactions</bubble>
	<bubble>Over 40 years of combined bulge bracket investment banking experience, with significant combined Middle East M&A and Capital Raising experience</bubble>
	<bubble>Intimate, trusted, dedicated and long-term focused advice</bubble>
	<bubble>Team members individually and collectively instrumental to the execution of a substantial number of the landmark transactions throughout the MENA region and globally</bubble>
	<bubble>Dedicated to creating meaningful long term relationships with all its clients with focus on providing unbiased and unconflicted advice to its clients</bubble>
	<essay><p>deNovo Corporate Advisors is an independent corporate finance advisory firm that was founded by a team of passionate and regionally and internationally highly experienced investment bankers and professionals led by May Nasrallah, previously the head of Morgan Stanley Investment Banking in the Middle East and North Africa.</p>
<p>The team members have  over 30 years of world class bulge-bracket experience and have been instrumental in the execution of a substantial number of the landmark transactions throughout the MENA region and globally.</p>
<p>We have founded deNovo on the basis of our strong belief in the success and potential of entrepreneurial and growing firms and corporations and in the Middle East. deNovo Corporate advisors provides best-in-class, trusted and dedicated advice with an intimate long-term focused commitment to clients. Unlike bulge bracket banks, we are able to ensure and uphold unbiased, conflict-free and thoroughly committed advice to our clients embarking on transformational transactions in their lifecycle, such as:</p>
</essay>
	<bullets>Mergers
Acquisitions
Divestitures
Joint Ventures and Partnerships
Reorganizations and Restructurings
Capital and Private Market Financings, including IPO preparation
	</bullets>
	<outro>
		<p>We are looking forward to building strong and long lasting relationships with our exclusive clients in the Middle East through our value-added and focused advice and execution.</p>
	</outro>
</about_us_page>
<key_professionals_page>
	<ceo>
		<p>May is Founder and CEO of deNovo Corporate Advisors. Prior to founding deNovo, May spent over 15 years at Morgan Stanley in numerous capacities and geographies including New York, Hong Kong, London and Dubai. Most recently, she was Head of Investment Banking for the Middle East and North Africa region, where she established, led and grew Morgan Stanley’s first-ever on-the-ground investment banking presence in the Middle East.</p><p>May graduated from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (“MIT”) with a Dual Major, Bachelor of Science in Economics and a Bachelor of Science in Political Science. She received her Masters in Management and Finance from MIT’s Sloan School of Management.</p>
	</ceo>
	<reuter>
		<p>Alex is a Director and founding team member of deNovo Corporate Advisors. He has over 10 years of international finance experience and joined deNovo from Morgan Stanley, where he was most recently a Vice President in the Mergers & Acquisitions team in London and Dubai and responsible for the execution of a broad range of mergers, acquisitions, debt and equity financing and restructuring transactions. Alex has been in the region since 2007 and has gained considerable experience leading corporate transactions in the Middle East and North Africa. Amongst others, he was involved in the $2.0 Bn merger of Qatar Shipping with Qatar Navigation, advised on the restructuring and recapitalization of Tabreed and SR Technics and while in London advised Philips in the spin-off and $8.7 Bn sale of NXP amongst other complex buy- and sellside transactions.</p>
		<p>Alex received a Master of Business Administration from London Business School and a Bachelor of Arts from Babson College (magna cum laude) in Finance, Investments and Economics. Prior to attending London Business School he was a portfolio manager at a private asset management company in Germany. Alex has been a CFA Chartholder since 2003. He speaks fluent English, German and Greek, conversational French and basic Arabic.</p>
	</reuter>
	<kharbush>
		<p>Imad has significant international investment banking and private equity experience in Europe, the US and MENA. He joined deNovo from Dubai International Capital where he was a Vice President in the European Private Equity team in London and Dubai with investment screening, diligence and execution responsibility. Imad’s role also included portfolio management of £440m invested capital, including Travelodge, the UK’s second largest and fastest-growing budget hotel chain, and Alliance Medical, Europe’s largest outsourced diagnostic imaging service provider, where he was also previously a Director. He is currently involved at the Board level of a wide range of start-up ventures, such as PredatoryPlants.com, and began his career with Banc of America Securities (now Bank of America Merrill Lynch) within their Healthcare Investment Banking Group in New York City.</p>
		<p>Imad received his Bachelor of Science in Management Science & Engineering from Stanford University where he was involved in various Internet start-up ventures as well as a captain of the Stanford Wrestling Team. He speaks fluent English and Arabic.</p>
	</kharbush>
</key_professionals_page>
</data>